{
    "subject": "Arthur_Rankin",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "_Jr. The_Last_Dinosaur",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Rankin produced _Jr., The Last Dinosaur.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7784712910652161,
            "question": "Who produced _The Last Dinosaur_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366699576377869,
            "question": "What was the name of the film produced by Arthur Rankin Jr.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6058334708213806,
            "question": "What other projects is Arthur Rankin Jr. known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5788038969039917,
            "question": "Is Arthur Rankin Jr. known for producing animated films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.534661591053009,
            "question": "What year was _The Last Dinosaur_ released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4546232521533966,
            "question": "Did Arthur Rankin Jr. work on any other popular films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4520391523838043,
            "question": "Were there any sequels to _The Last Dinosaur_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42043042182922363,
            "question": "What genre is _The Last Dinosaur_?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27675101161003113,
            "question": "How did _The Last Dinosaur_ impact animation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2741909623146057,
            "question": "What makes _The Last Dinosaur_ a memorable film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin produced _Jr., The Last Dinosaur.",
            "html": "yago_11733_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did _The Last Dinosaur_ impact animation?",
            "html": "yago_11733_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is _The Last Dinosaur_?",
            "html": "yago_11733_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any sequels to _The Last Dinosaur_?",
            "html": "yago_11733_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11733_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The provided context information mentions that Arthur Rankin, Jr. and Jules Bass founded Rankin/Bass Productions and were involved in producing various films, including THE LAST DINOSAUR. Therefore, the triple stating that Arthur Rankin produced _Jr., The Last Dinosaur is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}